JOHN PARK

Orlando, FL · 407-953-9116 **Jpark103193@gmail.com**

Focused Research Assistant well-versed in conducting laboratory, library and field research. Adept at working within collaborative environments to gather and processes research data for diverse projects as well as literature reviews, data synthesis and analysis.

EXPERIENCE

DATES FROM MARCH 2019 TO PRESENT

SR. LAB ANALYST/RESEARCH ASSISTANT, SANOFI PASTEUR VAXDESIGN

- Provided observations and performed tests at various stages according to SOP Standards.
- Analyze data via utilization of multiple forms of assays and instrumentation (i.e. Flow Cytometry, MSD, ELISA, etc...).
- Aid Senior Scientists and Research Associates in documentation and reports of experiments and procedures.

DATES FROM FEBRUARY 2018 TO FEBRUARY 2019 LAB TECHNICIAN, ENCOLABS

- Logged Sample information and recorded results into system using LIMS (Laboratory Information Management System.
- Proficient in the process of Good Manufacturing Practices (GMP) and Good Laboratory Practices (GLP) via OSHA and EPA standards.
- Use existing procedures to perform daily hands-on calibration work, ensuring calibrations are performed as scheduled and as defined by calibration program SOP's.

EDUCATION

AUGUST 2013-MAY 2017

BACHELORS OF SCIENCE: CHEMISTRY, UNIVERSITY OF CENTRAL FLORIDA

- Coursework in Physical, Inorganic and Biochemical Chemistry
- Field of Interest include: Solid State Materials, Application of Materials for both Biological and Physical Studies, and Data Analysis and Statistics.

SKILLS

- Experimental Development
- Literature Reviews
- Specimen Handling
- Instrumentation (Assays, Flow Cytometry, MSD etc....)
- Research and Analysis
- LIMS and Microsoft Office Expertise
- Research reporting and Documentation
- Wet Chemistry Techniques